A Guide to The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records, [1977-1990]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records [1977-1990]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.902
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1990 July 11.
Contents List
- Audit Committee-Correspondence 1987 (Box 1)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee-Correspondence (2 folders) [1985-1986] (Box 1)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee-Minutes [1990] (Box 1)
- Committee Agenda 1988 (Box 1)
- Educational Policy Committee-Correspondence 1987 (Box 1)
- Educational Policy Committee-Minutes [1990] (Box 1)
- Executive Committee-Correspondence [1986-1987] (Box 1)
- Finance Committee (1 of 2) [1986-1988] (Box 1)
- Finance Committee (2 of 2) [1986-1988] (Box 2)
- Finance Committee-Correspondence (3 folders) 1987 (Box 2)
- Finance Committee-Minutes [1990] (Box 2)
- Health Affairs Committee-Minutes [1990] (Box 2)
- Investment Banker Selection Committee [1983] (Box 2)
- Medical Center Council of Trustees [1986-1988] (Box 2)
- Medical Center Council of Trustees-Minutes (1 of 3) [1977-1984] (Box 2)
- Medical Center Council of Trustees-Minutes (2-3 of 3) [1977-1984] (Box 3)
- Special Committee on Fraternity and Sorority Housing (3 folders) [1983-1985] (Box 3)
- Special Committee of the BOV on the Nomination of a Chancellor [1984] (Box 3)
- Special Committee of the Board of Visitors on Real Estate (2 folders) [1985-1986] (Box 4)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee-Correspondence [1985-1987] (Box 4)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee-Minutes [1990] (Box 4)
- University of Virginia Real Estate Foundation [1986] (Box 4)